♪♪～
What was that?
（アラジン・心の声）
≪なんだろう？　今　一瞬だけ→
It was only for a split second, but
that man appeared to be a black sun.
あの人が
黒い太陽に見えた気がした≫
♪♪～
ウーゴくん？
Ugo?
♪♪～
akogare wo ima tsukanda
My desires are within reach.
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
ashita kara umare kawaru toka
People say they'll change the next day.
♪♪～
dareka ga mikiri tsuketa toka
But they give up so easily.
kono machi no style toka
That's just how it is here.
sonna mono ni nagasare tsuzukete
They get swept away by those excuses day by day.
kado no toreta genseki ni ha
They're nothing more than a chip, swept off the edge
kitto daremo you ha nai
and no longer needed by anyone.
♪♪～
fushigi to tobira no mukou ni ha
Guess what? Out there,
v.i.p nanoru yatsu ha naku
no one's swaggering around like a VIP.
daremo ga kunou no hate sa ore mo
Everyone suffers their own heartaches, myself included.
akogare wo ima tsukanda
But my desires are within reach.
♪♪～
mi wo yudanereba ii  kaji ha kono te ni
Throw yourself in with abandon. I've got the wheel.
mitsu kazoete the show time
On the count of three, it's show time!
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
♪♪～
≫コツ　コツ　コツ　コツ（足音）
10th Night
His Name is Judal
Oh? You're already entertaining visitors?
（マルッキオ）おや？　先客ですか？
The King of Sindria, Sinbad, called in on us. Introduce yourself.
（アブマド）
来訪中のシンドリア国王殿だ。→
挨拶せい。
（アリババ）待てよ！
Wait, I'm the one who's-
今は　俺が…。
（シンドバッド）アリババ君。
Alibaba.
はぁ…。
♪♪～
（マルッキオ）はじめまして。
銀行屋のマルッキオと申します。→
I am Markkio the Banker. Pleased to meet you.
I act as the adviser on financial affairs here in Balbadd.
バルバッドの財政顧問を
請け負っております。
I am Sinbad, King of Sindria. It's a pleasure.
（シンドバッド）シンドリア国国王
シンドバッドです。
よろしく。
こちらこそ。
Pleasure's all mine.
Have we met before?
どこかで　お会いしたことが？
No, this is the first time.
いいえ。
あなたとは　初対面ですよ。
Is it now?
（シンドバッド）そうですか。
≫（ジュダル）ああ～　どけって　もう！→
I said move it!
Seriously, what is with this stupid swarm of people?
何なんだよ
このうぜぇ人混みはよぉ。
なっ！
（ジュダル）おっ　バカ殿じゃん！→
Woah! It's Lord Bonehead!
What're you doing here?
なんで　いんだよ？　お前　いっつも
俺の邪魔しに　現れんだよなぁ。
You always mess up my plans!
Judal, what are you doing here?
（シンドバッド）
ジュダル　お前こそ　なぜ？
ああ～
俺　今　煌帝国で　神官やってんの。
I'm the Priest over at the Kou Empire.
The Kou Empire?
（シンドバッド）お前が　煌帝国の？
（ジュダル）ああ。→
Yeah, and today, I'm here on business for them.
今日は　そのお勤めでさ。→
よっ　来たぜ。
（マルッキオ）ふふふっ。
Yo, I'm here.
（シンドバッド）
≪ジュダルが　煌帝国に。→
Judal is a part of the Kou Empire...
Which means that that man must also be...
ということは　あの男も…≫
（ジュダル）で　何やんの？
So what's up?
I will explain shortly.
（マルッキオ）後ほど　ご説明いたします。
Sorry, but could you leave now, King Sinbad?
（アブマド）
悪いけど　シンドバッドおじさん→
もう帰ってほしいでし。
Our conversation has not yet come to a conclusion.
（シンドバッド）まだ話は終わっていない。
そうだ！
Yeah!
If you're talking about reopening trade
with Sindria, I'm afraid that's just impossible.
（アブマド）
シンドリアとの貿易再開なら→
ほんとに無理でしよ。
（シンドバッド）どういうことだ？
What do you mean?
I've already handed Balbadd's
trading rights over to the Kou Empire.
バルバッドの貿易の権限は→
すべて
煌帝国に　渡すことにしたでし。
あっ…。
（アブマド）だから　煌帝国が→
So I can't conduct trade with any
country not approved by the Kou Empire.
許可しない国とは
貿易できないでし。
Do you plan on becoming a jurisdiction of the Kou Empire?
（シンドバッド）
煌帝国に　支配されるつもりか!?
No.
（アブマド）そうじゃないでし。
これは　銀行屋が→
The Banker suggested I take this measure in
order to try and improve Balbadd's economy.
バルバッドの経済回復のために→
提案した政策なんでし。
（マルッキオ）そうです。
That is right.
国と国との
平和的な経済の橋渡し→
It is a Banker's job to act as a mediator between countries,
それが　私たち銀行屋の仕事。→
so as to achieve a peaceful economic balance.
That's right! As a king yourself, would you be interested?
そうだ…　あなたも
国王様なのでしたら　どうです？→
Would you like to entrust everything to us Bankers?
私たちに
すべてを任せてみませんか？
くっ…　おい！
俺の話だって　終わってねぇぞ！
Hey! I'm not done talking to you either!
国王として　約束しろよ！
Promise me as the King of Balbadd!
苦しんでる人たちを　絶対守るって。
Promise me that you'll help all of those who are suffering!
ふあぁ～…。
スラムのゴミの言葉など
僕には　分からないでし。
I don't speak Slum, you trash.
♪♪～
You...
お前…。
お前と俺たちに　違いなんてねぇ！
We're all the same!
（シンドバッド）やめろ！
一旦　退くんだ　アリババ君！
Stop.
Ahbmad!
Let's withdraw for now, Alibaba!
Let me go!
聞けよ！　ちくしょ～～!!
Face me, dammit!
どうなったの？
アリババ様…。
How did it go?
Lord Alibaba was...
（ざわめき）
（Ｌナンド）に…　にいちゃん
なんなの？　この空気。
Brother, why's everyone so weird?
Looks like negotiations failed.
（Ｍナンド）会談は
失敗に終わったのでしょうね。
（Ｓナンド）だなぁ。
Yeah.
Alibaba, were you able to talk with the King?
アリババくん
王様とは　話せたのかい？
That wasn't a talk.
話どころじゃなかったよ。
アブマド兄さんは
シンドバッドとばっか話すし→
My brother, Ahbmad, would only talk to Sinbad.
And, in the end, we couldn't change anything.
結局　なんにもならなかった。
そんなことないよ。
聞こえるだろ？
That's not true.
Can't you hear them?
アリババ様！
アリババ様～！
Prince Alibaba!
アリババ様！
会談は　どうなったんですか!?
How were the negotiations?
教えてください　アリババ様！
Please tell us, Prince Alibaba!
君が　王様と話したことで→
Your talks with the King touched so many people.
あんなに　たくさんの人が
心動かされたんだ。
You changed the people's hearts today.
今日　君が変えたことが
確かにあるよ。
ありがとう　アラジン。
Thanks Aladdin.
But what do we do now?
（モルジアナ）
でも　これから　どうしましょう？
I think the Fog Troupe and the people outside need to be informed as to what happened.
霧の団や　外にいる人たちに→
事情を知らせないわけには
いかないように思います。
はぁ…　交渉決裂だなんて→
How do I tell them that the negotiations completely broke down?
どう伝えりゃいいんだ…。
そうだね。
Well...
≫コン　コン（ノック）
≫ガチャ（ドアの音）
（ジャーファル）来てください。　シンが
今日の結果を伝えるそうです。
Come.
Sin is going to announce the results of today's negotiations.
♪♪～
（ジャーファル）さあ　頭領の君も。
Go. You're leading this too.
うっ　うわっ…。
さあ　アリババ君。
Come, Alibaba.
（シンドバッド）
諸君　本日の会談交渉は　決裂した。
Men.
Today's negotiations completely broke down.
ああ…。
そんな…。
（シンドバッド）
要求は　完全に　はねのけられた。→
Our demands were wholly ignored.
A clash between the imperial army and our forces is inevitable.
国王軍と我々の対立は
決定的となってしまった。
Kassim and his group have left us...
≫（団員）カシムたちも
出ていっちまったしよぉ。
≫（団員）
もう　俺たち　おしまいだぜ…。
We're done for...
（シンドバッド）何が　おしまいなんだ？
（一同）あっ…。
What's done for?
（シンドバッド）これまでは　盗賊まがいの
やり方しかなかった君たちが→
Today, for the first time, you fought fairly and openly,
instead of as thieves in the mists.
今日　初めて
正々堂々と戦ったんだろう。
Do not forget the reason you decided to fight!
自分が　剣を取った理由を思い出せ。
To escape from overwhelming poverty, to support your families.
貧しさから抜け出すこと
守るべき家族を養うこと…。
こんなもので
終わりだと思うヤツが→
Does anyone here think those things are now done for?
この場に　一人でもいるのか？
あっ。
≪（団員）ははっ…　そうだよな！
≪（団員）やってやろうぜ！
（シンドバッド）よし。→
Right. Then I will lend you all of my power.
ならば　俺は
俺の持てる力のすべてを→
お前たちに貸そう。
No matter what happens, I will overcome it!
何が来ようが　俺が倒してやる。
国を追われようなら
俺の国で　受け入れてやる。
If you are driven out by your country, then I will accept you into mine.
世界は
まだ　理不尽さであふれている。
The world is still filled with too many unreasonable things.
それと戦う者たちを受け入れる。→
I accept all those who will stand against such inequalities!
That is why I created a nation.
そのために
俺は　国を作ったのだから。
（一同）ああ…。
あっ。
≪（団員）よし！
All right!
≫（団員）よし　頑張ろうぜ！
≫（団員）ああ！
We'll be okay!
≫（団員）大丈夫よ。
≫（団員）ははははっ！
♪♪～
A King really is something else.
（団員）
やっぱ　一国の王様って　すげぇな。
Yeah, he's meant to lead people!
（団員）ああ。　あれが
人の上に立つ人間なんだな。
（団員）頼りにしてるぜ。
んん…。
Alibaba...
アリババくん…。
ん？　どうしたの!?　ウーゴくん！
What's the matter, Ugo?
≫（ジュダル）おい　シンドバッド！
（シンドバッド）ん？
Hey, Sinbad!
（ジュダル）こんな所に
いやがったのか　バカ殿。
So this is where you were hiding, Lord Bonehead.
（シンドバッド）ジュダル。
Judal!
（ジュダル）ここで　何してんの？
あいつは　昼間の。
What're you doing here?
He was at the palace!
♪♪～
ジュダル　お前
アブマドの手先として　来たのか？
Judal, are you here on behalf of Ahbmad?
（ジュダル）はあ？
それとも　煌帝国のか？
No.
Or for the Kou Empire?
（ジュダル）ああ～　違う　違う。
Nope, wrong again.
To be honest, I don't care about either of them.
正直　俺
そういうの　どうでもいいから。
（シンドバッド）
この国で　一体　何をする気だ？
Why are you here?
（ジュダル）さあ？
俺には　経済ってのは興味ねぇ。→
Good question. I have no interest in economics.
それより　俺が好きなのは…→
What I really care about is war.
戦争だよ。
くっ！
The Kou Empire is really strong!
強いんだぜ　煌帝国は。
兵隊も　たくさんいる。
They have tons of soldiers.
迷宮攻略者は　５人もいるし→
And five Dungeon Capturers!
迷宮怪物軍団もできたんだ。
They've even created a battalion of dungeon creatures!
はははっ　すごいだろ！
Isn't that cool?
Damn Kou...
貴様ら…。
（ジュダル）ああ～　勘違いすんなよ。
Don't get the wrong idea now.
俺が　いちばん組みたいのは
シンドバッド→
You're the one who I want to team up with the most, Sinbad.
お前なんだぜ。
だから　いいかげん→
So hurry up and get over here and
let's work on taking over the world!
俺と組んで…。
ジャーファルおにいさん　あの人は？
Mister Jafar, who is he?
His name is Judal.
彼は　ジュダル。
我々と　因縁のある男だ。
We have a long relationship.
あなたと同じ　マギですよ。
（シンドバッド）俺は　お前らの→
He's a Magi just like you.
操り人形にはならん。
えっ？　マギ？
What? A Magi?
You're still saying that?
ははっ！　また　その返事かよ。
ん？
あっ。
何？　こいつ。
Who's that?
He has strange rukh around him.
こいつの周りのルフ　変だぜ。
はぁ…　お前と同じ　マギだ。
He's a Magi, like you.
はあ～!?　こんなチビが　マギ!?
What?!
That little shrimp is a Magi?
うそだろ～？
マギってのは　すげぇんだぜ。→
No way!
Magi are supposed to be amazing!
創世の魔法使いにして
最強の魔力の使者。
They're world-creating magicians and the most powerful magoi users!
そんなのが　俺のほかに
そうそういて　たまるかよ。
There can't be another one besides me!
（シンドバッド）彼が　マギだから→
He's a Magi too. That's why you noticed him, isn't it?
お前も反応したんだろ。
（ジュダル）ん？
ふっ！　よう　チビ。
うわっ…。
Hey, little Magi.
（ジュダル）俺は　ジュダル。　お前は？
I'm Judal.
Who're you?
あっ　ああ…　僕は　アラジン。
H-Hi. I'm Aladdin.
そっかぁ　アラジン
マギ同士　よろしくな。
Hey Aladdin.
Nice to meet you, my fellow Magi.
ガッ！
（一同）あっ！
♪♪～
Well now, not too bright, is he?
（ジュダル）おい　おい　鈍くせぇな。
アラジン！
Aladdin!
You don't plan on teaming up with this guy, do you?
こんなヤツと
組む気じゃねぇだろうな？
We just met by coincidence.
（シンドバッド）
彼とは　偶然　出会っただけだ。→
関係ない。
（ジュダル）ならいいけど。→
He's not involved.
As long as that's the case.
Oh yeah. So who's your King Candidate, huh kid?
そうだ　チビ
お前の王候補を出せよ。
王候補？
（ジュダル）その辺に→
King Candidate?
You surely have at least one or two.
１人か２人くらい　いんだろ？
なんだ　だんまりかよ。
No answer?
いいよ～　じゃあ　自分で探すから。
Fine, I'll search them out myself.
♪♪～
（ジュダル）見～つけた。
あっ！
Found him.
Wait! You're that guy Ahbmad was making fun of this afternoon!
って…　なんだ　お前。
昼間　アブマドに→
いじめられてたヤツじゃん。
はははっ！　みっともなかったな。
You were a mess!
必死こいて　わめいてたけど
全然　聞いてもらえなくて。→
You were yelling and screaming so
desperately but he didn't even look at you.
You teared up a little at the end, didn't you?
しまいにゃ
ほんと泣いてたもんな。→
お前って　情けないヤツ…。
You're so pathetic.
He is not!
情けなくなんかない！
（ジュダル）ああ？
アラジン…。
Aladdin!
アリババくんは
情けなくなんかない。
Alibaba is not pathetic.
僕は知っている。　アリババくんは→
He knew that there was a chance he wouldn't be acknowledged.
自分が
認められないかもって知ってたよ。
けど　みんなのために行ったんだ。
But he still went! So he could help everyone!
誰もできなかったことを
やりに行ったんだ！
He went to do the impossible!
He's a hero!
アリババくんは
勇気ある人なんだ！
Aladdin...
アラジン…。
へえ～　チビ→
Geez kid, you're really expecting a lot from your King Candidate.
そんなに見込んでる
王候補なのかよ。
ふ～ん。
俺には　そうは見えないけど。
I don't see it.
あっ…　うっ！
あっ！
ほ～ら　弱ぇ。
アリババくん！
See? He's a weakling.
Alibaba!
アリババさん！
（シンドバッド）ジュダル！
Alibaba!
Judal!
Yo, why are you with these losers?
なあ！　なんで
こんな　くっだらねぇヤツらと→
つるんでんの？　バッカじゃねぇ。
So stupid.
♪♪～
ふっ　やる気かよ。
Wanna go?
♪♪～
At the beginning, it was just a feeling.
≪最初は　なんとなくだった≫
But now I'm certain.
≪でも　今は　はっきりと分かる≫
I must stop this person.
≪僕は
この人を　止めなくてはならない≫
Looks like you do.
戦う気満々みてぇだなぁ　おい。
I don't want to fight you, but if you plan on attacking us again, I will stop you.
君と戦いたいわけじゃないけど→
これ以上
僕たちに何かするなら　止めるよ。
ふっ！
（シンドバッド）やめるんだ　二人とも！
Stop, both of you!
Be quiet, Sinbad.
黙ってな　シンドバッド。
これは　マギ同士の戦い。
This is a fight between Magi.
ただの人間には　口出し無用。→
Normal humans stay out.
Besides, you can't stop me right now, can you?
それに　今のあんたに
俺は　止められないね。→
分かってるぜ。　今
金属器　一つも持ってねぇんだろ？
I can tell. You're not carrying a single Metal Vessel.
くっ！　マスルール。
（マスルール）了解。
Masrur!
Understood.
くっ！
He's right.
やっぱり　ダメです。　俺たち　今→
We're no good if we can't access the power of the Metal Vessels.
眷属器　使えないんで。
くそ！
Dammit!
ふっ！
さあ　始めようぜ　チビのマギ。
Let's do it, little Magi!
Round one, magoi shots!
まずは
魔力の撃ち合いといこうぜ。
んん…。
魔力の撃ち合い？
Magoi shots?
（ジュダル）さあ　いくぜ！
Here I go!
（団員たち）うわっ！
（Ｓナンド）おお～！
はははっ！　穴だらけになりやがれ。
I'll shoot holes in everything!
あっ？
I see.
（ジュダル）なんだ　そっか…。→
Hey, let's stop.
おい　チビ　やめよう。→
魔力の撃ち合いは　意味がねぇ。
There's no meaning in us shooting magoi.
As Magi, we're protected by the rukh. It looks like our magoi will just negate each other.
ルフの加護があるマギ同士じゃ→
魔力が
打ち消し合っちまうみてぇだ。
≪魔力が　打ち消し合う？≫
Our magoi will negate each other?
In that case, then let's fight with magic!
こうなったら　魔法で勝負だ。
魔法？
なんだ→
Magic?
Aren't you supposed to be a Magi?
知らねぇのか？　マギのくせに。
俺が教えてやるよ　チビ。
Well kid, if you don't know, I guess I'll have to teach you.
魔力とはな
ルフが生み出す　純然たる力。→
Magoi is pure power created from the rukh.
If you gather it and shoot it in that form, it's not very strong.
魔力は　そのまま集めて撃っても
大した威力はねぇ。→
さっきみたいに
ちょっと物を壊す程度だが→
As you saw earlier, it'll just break a few things.
But if you give a command to the rukh...
魔力を生み出すルフたちに
とある命令を与えると…。
♪♪～
You can do this!
（ジュダル）
このとおり　雷魔法の完成だぜ！
Lightning magic!
（３人）あっ！
くっ…。　あっ！
ドォーーン!!
♪♪～
おい　おい
あっさり吹き飛んじまったのか？→
Did you go flying? That was too easy.
あっ！
はぁ　はぁ…　これが　魔法。
So this is magic.
♪♪～
へえ～
チビ　面白ぇの持ってんじゃん。→
Wow kid. Quite the thing you've got there.
巨大なジンの体…　そんなもん→
Only a Magi can substantiate the giant body of a djinn.
俺たちマギにしか
出せねぇもんなぁ。
いいぜ
認めてやるよ　お前のこと。→
I guess I have to accept that you're a Magi.
But my magic isn't limited to just that.
でも　俺の魔法だって
あんなもんじゃないんだぜ。
♪♪～
（ジュダル）バルバッドは　霧の町。→
Balbadd is a city of fog.
水なら　いくらでも集められる。
Here, I can gather as much water as I want.
And if I give this a command as well...
そして　更に　命令すると…。
♪♪～
You'll have the honor of seeing my specialty, ice magic!
（ジュダル）
俺のいちばん得意な氷魔法だ！
（Ｍナンド）あぁ…。
（Ｌナンド）にいちゃん　でっかい氷！
Brother! That ice is huge!
（Ｓナンド）バカ野郎！
その前に　なんで　あいつ→
Idiot, you should be more concerned about him floating!
飛んでんだ!?
Suspension magic.
≪浮遊魔法か。　複数の魔法を→
He can use multiple types of magic at the same time. What power.
同時に使うとは…　なんてヤツだ≫
ははははっ！
驚くのは　まだ早いぜ。
Don't be so easily impressed!
俺の得意技は　これからさ。
I haven't even shown you my special trick yet!
♪♪～
（一同）おおっ…。
Take this! Sang Arsarros!
くらえ！　「降り注ぐ氷槍」！
ドン　ドン　ドン！　ドン　ドン！
（一同）うわ～！
うわぁ～！
ああ～！
あっ！
バキン！
へえ～　やるじゃん。
Not bad!
But what're you gonna do now?
でも　これなら　どうだ？
あっ…　ウーゴくん！
Ugo!
あっ？
ううっ！　うわぁ～！
♪♪～
（ジャーファル）これが　マギ同士の戦い。
So this is a fight between Magi.
They're both strong.
（シンドバッド）≪どちらも強い。
アラジンも　引けを取らない。→
Aladdin does not fail to stand up to Judal.
But...
しかし…≫
はははっ　強ぇじゃん　そいつ。→
You're strong!
But you're not out of the woods yet.
でも　これで
勝った気になってんじゃねぇよな？
I've still got plenty where that came from.
俺の氷は　まだ残ってんだぜ。
あっ！
ドドドドドッ！
ああっ！
ウーゴくん！
（ジュダル）ははっ！　バカだ　こいつ。
Ugo!
He's an idiot.
ウーゴさんが…。
アラジン…。
Ugo!
Aladdin!
力を…　力をあげなきゃ。
Take my strength!
すぅ～…　ふぅ～！
はぁ　はぁ…。
♪♪～
That djinn's amazing.
とんでもねぇな　そいつ。
でも　効いたみたいだぜ。　見ろよ→
But even he couldn't get away unscathed.
Take a look.
He's leaking magoi from his wounds.
穴から　魔力が漏れてる。
あっ！
ウーゴくん　ウーゴくん！　くっ…。
Ugo! Ugo!
Why?
なぜなんだ!?　なぜ　君は　僕たちに
こんなことをするんだい!?
Why are you doing this to us?
なんで？
"Why?"
そういや
なんで戦ってんだっけ？→
Why are we fighting again?
I guess it doesn't matter.
まあ　いいじゃねぇか。
お前も　マギなら分かるだろ。
Since you're a Magi too, you understand.
I'm just so full of power that I don't know what to do with it all!
俺は　力が　余って余って
しょうがねぇんだよ。
And every single day is so mind-numbingly boring!
おかげで
毎日が　クソつまんねぇけど→
でも　今日は
ちょっとだけ楽しいぜ！→
But hey, I kinda had fun today!
So play with me some more, little Magi!
だから
もっと　俺と遊べよ　チビのマギ！
What's wrong with him?
≪何なんだ？　あの人…≫
あっ…　ああっ！
Ugo, it's fine! Just return to the flute!
もういいよ！　戻って　ウーゴくん。
Return! Hurry!
戻って…　戻ってよ！
ウーゴくん！　あっ！
Ugo!
うっ…。　ウーゴくん!!
Why won't he return?
≪なぜ戻らないの!?　それに→
I've already stopped feeding him power!
僕は　もう　力あげてないのに→
ウーゴくんが　止まってくれない≫
Ugo won't stop!
Hey kid! Don't tell me you're done already.
おい　チビ！　まさか
これで終わりじゃねぇよな？
Ugo!
ウーゴくん…　ウーゴくん！
（ウーゴ・回想）
((よかったのか？　アラジン))
Are you sure that's what you want to
wish for? To become friends with me?
((俺と友達になるなんて
願い事をして))
((いいのさ。
僕の　たった一人の大切な友達を→
Yes. Cause I can't leave my one and only friend behind!
置いてはいけないからね))
((あっ…))
((ふふっ))
Ugo, you're a really important friend to me. So please listen!
ウーゴくん
君は　僕の大切な友達なのさ。
だから　言うことを聞いて！
≪（ジュダル）おい　チビ！
Hey kid!
こんな機会　めったにないんだ。
I almost never get chances like this.
もっともっと遊ぼうぜ。
Let's play more!
ドン！
大丈夫ですか？　アラジン。
モルさん。
Are you all right, Aladdin?
Morg!
おお～　なんだ？　その女。
すげぇ速いじゃん。
What's up with her? She was so fast!
こっちだ　イカレ野郎！
ん？
Over here, you lunatic!
でやぁ～～!!
バリバリバリッ！
だから～　俺に
普通の攻撃は　効かねぇんだよ。
Normal attacks don't work on me, remember?
てやっ！
あっ！
ぐっ！
パリン！
なっ！
くっ！
はぁ…。
痛ぇな！
That hurt!
I forgot. You're a Dungeon Capturer.
（ジュダル）忘れてたよ。
お前　迷宮攻略者だったな。
うっ！
バキン！
（２人）あっ！
アリババ君！
Alibaba!
（ジュダル）邪魔すんなよ！
（２人）あっ。
Stay out of it!
I'm gonna fight that Magi until I'm
satisfied, and then I'm gonna kill him!
俺は　マギ同士で
思う存分　戦ってから→
あのチビを
ぶち殺してぇんだからな！
♪♪～
ドゴン！
（ジュダル）はぁ　はぁ…。→
なんだよ？　一体。　ああっ！
What was that?
（ジュダル）おお～～！→
ぐわぁ～～!!→
ぐっ！　うわぁ～…。
ドゴン！
♪♪～
ウーゴくん…。
Ugo...
♪♪～
ああっ…　あっ!?→
ちょ…　ちょっと待て！
何なんだよ!?　このジンは！→
What's the matter with this djinn?!
ぐっ！
ドゴン！
Ugo, stop!
ウーゴくん　もうやめて！
Look, kid. Using that djinn is cheating.
おい　チビ！
そのジン　卑怯だぞ。→
You haven't been giving him any magoi for a while now, right?
さっきから　お前　自分の魔力を→
そいつに　やってねぇだろ！
バキン　バキン　バキン　バキン！
That means he's moving on someone else's magoi!
そいつ　今　ほかのヤツの魔力で
動いてるってことだ。
Meaning he's not your djinn!
つまり
そのジンは　お前のジンじゃねぇ！
♪♪～
ドスッ！
ああっ！
I win.
勝った。
なっ!?
ウーゴくん！
Ugo!
くっ！　ううっ…。
あっ！
バン！
（３人）あっ！
（２人）あぁ…。
あっ。
ウーゴくん…。
Ugo...
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
me ni mieru sekai ha subete kako no monogatari sa
The world you see before your eyes is a story already told.
♪♪～
kagayaku mirai wo miushinau na yo
Don't lose sight of the bright future ahead.
♪♪～
kimi ni ha motto ippai yume to kibou ga arun da
You're destined to realize great hopes and dreams.
bootto shitetara minogashichau zo
But if you blink for too long, they'll leave you behind.
♪♪～
dekinai riyuu sagasu yori
Instead of searching for an excuse,
yatte mireba ii
why not just give it a try?
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
yubi to yubi wo marume ryoume ni ate
Make circles with your fingers and put them around your eyes.
imeeji shite sagashiteru mono
Picture your hopes and dreams!
♪♪～
atama no naka no adobenchaaa
Picture your personal adventure story!
doko he mukau?
Where are you headed?
yubi bouenkyou
What can you see
♪♪～
yubi no sono sukima ni nani ga mieru?
in the space between your fingers?
tooi you demo hontou ha chikai
It might seem far, but it's really not.
yogen no you na takaramono
It's a promise as valuable as any treasure!
Who hurt our cute little Judal?
Please stop, my lady.
Based on your appearance, you must be a lady of the Kou Empire.
Next time: A New Visitor.
11th Night
A New Visitor
Ugo! This can't be, Ugo!
（紅玉）かわいいジュダルちゃんを
いじめたのは　だ～れ？
（シンドバッド）やめてくれ　お嬢さん。
煌帝国の姫君と　お見受けするが。
おい　ウーゴくん…。
うそだろ!?　ウーゴくん！
北朝鮮が人工衛星の打ち上げと称
している
長距離弾道ミサイルの発射実験に
ついて、
時期の調整を検討していると発表
した。
これについて韓国政府当局は、
技術的な問題が発生し、